

MA-336, College Ring 6, Bremen, 28759, Germany

□ (+49) 1511-5661770 | ■ theparthshukla@gmail.com | 🕏 www.parthshukla.me | 🖸 theparthshukla | 🛅 theparthshukla

"Do, or do not. There is no try."

Summary _

Creative and engaged third year Computer Science student with experience in design and backend development. Interested in using my passion for problem solving to build better solutions for challenging tasks and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Education

Jacobs University B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Bremen, Germany

Aug. 2019 - Present

Work Experience _____

Solactive AG Berlin, Germany

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Sep. 2020 - Present

- · Designed, prototyped and implemented business specific data objects, production-facing tools, libraries and services.
- Adopted and refactored existing business processes
- Structured and automated operational workflows
- · Heavily expanded test-coverage and took responsibility for monitoring and resolving test related issues for the weekly releases.

UWC Mahindra College Pune.India

SECRETARY OF THE COLLEGE ASSEMBLY

Mar. 2018 - Jan. 2019

- Facilitated, supported, and coordinated all activities of the student council.
- Developed, promoted, and conducted a variety of extra curricular programs for students.
- · Organized and coordinated various fundraising programs and funfair events to generate revenue.
- Planned, arranged, and chaired all meetings with council members, as needed.

Leave No Fingerprints Mumbai,India

HEAD OF MANAGEMENT AND ORGANISATION

Mar. 2017 - June. 2019

- · Organised multiple comedy events and concerts to raise money for purchasing equipment and dialysis machines for local hospitals.
- Developed and maintained the front end functionality of websites.

Honors & Awards

2018	Runner Up, T.C.S IT Wiz	Pune,India
2017	Da Vinci Scholar, World Scholar's Cup	Delhi, India
2017	1st Place, CISCE National Debate Final	Kolkata,India
2017	Student of The Year, Anand Niketan School	Ahmedabad, India

Skills____

Programming Experienced: Python, Java, JavaScript Basic: C, C++, Haskell

Tools Experienced: Git, LaTeX, Grafana

Front-end Experienced: HTML5, CSS Basic: React, Vue **Languages** Native: English, Hindi Basic: German

Extracurricular Activity _____

Computers for All Pune, India

Aug. 2017 - Jan. 2019 SERVICE PROGRAM CO-ORDINATOR

· Set up a functional computer lab and gave basic computer education to people of all age groups in the village of Asade.

PARTH SHUKLA · RÉSUMÉ OCTOBER 12, 2021